Guide to the Kate Bornstein papers 1910-2018
Brown University Library
Kate Bornstein papers
Bornstein (Kate) papers
1910-2018
John Hay Library University Archives and Manuscripts Box A Brown University Providence, RI 02912 Telephone: Manuscripts: 401-863-3723; University Archives: 401-863-2148 Email: Manuscripts: hay@brown.edu; University Archives: archives@brown.edu
Bornstein, Kate, 1948-
Christine Dunlap Farnham Archives
Pembroke Center for Teaching and Research on Women
MS.2018.010
20 Linear feet (18 record center cartons, 2 oversize file boxes)
This collection consists of the papers of Kate Bornstein, performer, playwright, author, and transgender activist who graduated from Brown University as Albert Bornstein in 1969. The collection documents Bornstein's personal and professional life and trans activism, and includes biographical information, correspondence, diaries, conference material, draft writings, writings by other authors, subject files, print material, ephemera, photographs, and electronic records dating from 1910-2018. The collection is arranged into 13 series.
Biographical / Historical
Katherine (Kate) Vandam Bornstein was born in Asbury Park, New Jersey on March 15, 1948 as Albert Herman Bornstein. Bornstein's parents, Mildred Vandam Bornstein and Paul Bornstein met while Mildred was attending Pembroke College in Brown University where she graduated in the class of 1939. Mildred and Paul married shortly thereafter and had a first child, Alan Bornstein, in approximately 1941. Paul Bornstein, a physician, served in North Africa during World War II as a medical administrator with the United States Army and the American Red Cross. Upon returning home, Mildred and Paul had a second son named Albert.
Interested in acting, the performing arts and writing from a young age, Albert attended Pennington School in New Jersey where he became the editor of the school yearbook. After high school, Albert chose to attend Brown University where a number of his relatives, including his mother, had also attended.
While at Brown, Bornstein intended to follow in his father's footsteps and study premed but quickly switched concentrations to English and theatre studies. Bornstein joined the Brownbrokers and Sock and Buskin organizations for performing arts and acted in various plays while on campus. Brown theater director, John Emigh, and Professor of Theatre Arts and Perfomrance Studies, James O. Barnhill, mentored Bornstein during Albert's tenure at Brown.
During childhood and Bornstein's college years, Bornstein acknowledged struggling less with sexuality but always with gender identity. Bornstein dated women throughout college and soon after graduation in 1968, Bornstein married for the first of three times, all of which ended in divorce. Bornstein is now partnered Barbara Carrellas, a notable sexologist and author of Urban Tantra (2007). The two have been partnered for over 20 years.
By the late 1970s and early 1980s, Albert Bornstein was struggling significantly with his gender identity. Married at the time to a woman named Molly and father to one daughter, Jessica Leah Bornstein (later Jessica Baxter), Albert followed Scientology while he and his family were living in New York. Albert Bornstein ascended throughout the ranks of the Church of Scientology notably becoming First Mate aboard L. Ron Hubbard's personal yacht, Apollo.
In 1981, Bornstein went to church elders to discuss his gender identity concerns but the church was unwelcoming. Bornstein left Scientology as a result of this discrimination. Around this time, Bornstein and his wife divorced while Molly and Jessica remained within the religion. Due in part to Scientology's restrictions on communications between past and current members, Bornstein has not seen Jessica in over 30 years.
In 1985, Albert Bornstein began the process of gender transition, including legally changing names from Albert Herman to Katherine Vandam Bornstein. Bornstein underwent sex reassignment surgery in 1986.
Bornstein worked in sales during this era and lived in various locations from Philadelphia to San Francisco to Seattle and later New York City. At the time, Bornstein was also writing about gender identity, both in fiction and non-fiction genres, speaking publicly, and participating in activism about transgenderism and being a trans person.
In 1995, Bornstein published the groundbreaking book, Gender Outlaw: On Men, Women, and the Rest of Us. The book became widely popular and propelled Kate to fame enabling her to begin performing and speaking professionally about gender identity issues, in theaters across the United States and often on college campuses. At the time, the United States was experiencing a post-Stonewall wave of civil rights for lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender people. Gender Outlaw and Bornstein's performance pieces gave voice to marginalized people at a flashpoint for that community.
Bornstein went on to publish other books, articles, and essays, including Nearly Roadkill with Caitlin Sullivan (1996), My Gender Workbook: How to Become a Real Man, a Real Woman, the Real You, or Something Else Entirely (1997), and Hello, Cruel World: 101 Alternatives to Suicide for Teens, Freaks, and Other Outlaws (2006). In 2012, Bornstein published A Queer and Pleasant Danger: A Memoir, where Bornstein wrote about personal family history, physical and mental health issues including disordered eating and bipolar disorder, and about being gender fluid and identifying neither as a man nor as a woman.
Exploring the constructs of gender and braking down binary gender barriers has been Bornstein's life work. As of 2018, Bornstein continues write and act, recently performing in Young Jean Lee's Broadway play, Straight White Male – the first Broadway play to be written by an Asian-American woman. Bornstein currently lives in East Harlem with Barbara Carrellas along with their two cats, a pug, and a turtle.
Names
Bornstein, Mildred Vandam; Brown University--Alumni and alumnae; Carrellas, Barbara; Christine Dunlap Farnham Archives; Pembroke Center for Teaching and Research on Women; Pembroke College (Brown University)--Alumni and alumnae
Subjects
Body image; Feminism -- United States -- 20th century; Gay rights; Gender identity; Lesbians; Mental health; Political activists -- United States; Scientology; Sex workers; Suicide Prevention; Theatre; Transgender people; World War II
RIAMCO Browsing Term
Race, Ethnicity and Gender
Collection information
This collection consists of the papers of Kate Bornstein, performer, playwright, author, and transgender activist who graduated from Brown University as Albert Bornstein in 1969. The collection documents Bornstein's personal and professional life and trans activism, and includes biographical information, correspondence, diaries, conference material, draft writings, writings by other authors, subject files, print material, ephemera, photographs, and electronic records dating from 1910-2018. The collection is arranged into 13 series.
Series I, BIOGRPAHICAL, 1910-2017, highlights Bornstein's biography and personal life. Materials include awards and honors, clippings about Kate Bornstein, Albert's Bornstein's birth certificate, Kate Bornstein's drivers licenses and identification cards, information regarding Bornstein's daughter, Jessica Leah Bornstein, interviews, and Bornstein's official name-change decree from Albert Herman Bornstein to Katherine Vandam Bornstein. Other materials of interest include an employment dispute file between Bornstein and Satellite Business Systems regarding Bornstein's transition and dress code in the workplace. There is also an extensive set of family letters that Bornstein's father, Paul Bornstein, wrote to Mildred Vandam Bornstein '39 [Bornstein's mother] while stationed in North Africa during World War II. This series is arranged alphabetically by record type then by topic.
Series 2, CORRESPONDENCE, 1977-2018, contains personal and professional correspondence, arranged alphabetically by provenance then by first name or subject. Scattered throughout the correspondence series are letters from family, friends, colleagues, and other trans artists, activists, students, and the general public thanking Kate for her leadership and advocacy on behalf of the trans community. Of particular interest are letters from Albert Bornstein to his mother, daughter, ex-wife, and a college friend from Brown University regarding his transgenderism dating from 1985-1986 (#3.1, 3.3-3.4).
Series 3, DIARIES AND NOTES, 1983-2015, contains bound diaries and a small set of loose personal notes. The diaries contain reflections, ideas for plays and scripts, notes for other writings, and personal lists and jottings. Series 3 is arranged alphabetically then chronologically.
Series 4, CONFERENCES, 1991-2017, includes programs, conference schedules, participant lists, and other related material regarding conferences that Bornstein attended or at which she spoke, often as a keynote speaker. Conferences include the Athe91 conference regarding theater studies in higher education; the 2000 Y2 Genders conference at Smith College, and the 2007 Queer Texas Conference, among many others. This series is arranged chronologically then alphabetically by the conference name.
Series 5, WRITINGS BY KATE BORNSTEIN, 1970-2013, includes drafts, some related correspondence, contracts, and promotional material regarding essays, manuscripts, plays, scripts, and talks written or co-written by Bornstein. Draft works of note include Hidden: A Gender (1989), Hello, Cruel World: 101 Alternatives to Suicide for Teens, Freaks, and Other Outlaws (2009), and A Queer and Pleasant Danger: A Memoir (2012). Essays include "Another American Legacy" regarding Condoleeza Rice, "Dixie Belle: The Further Adventures of Huckleberry Finn," and "Sex, Bullies and You: How American Bully Culture Is Messing with Your Sex Life." Researchers seeking talks by Bornstein should see the folders labeled "Various titles: talks, [dates]" (#9.7-9.16). Given the number of lectures Bornstein wrote and presented across the United States, they have been arranged chronologically within this series under the general heading noted here. Overall, Series 5 is arranged alphabetically by title then alphabetically by record type.
Series 6, WRITINGS BY OTHER AUTHORS (UNPUBLISHED), 1986-2014, includes drafts and correspondence related to essays, manuscripts, poems, scripts and various creative writing by other authors. Many of these writers are notable trans people and friends of Bornstein who sent their works to Bornstein for advice and review. Works of note include Butch Is a Noun by Sharon Jill Bear Bergman; Transgender MANifesto by Michael M Hernandez; poems by Cheryl Lynne Oropal; and scripts from the television series Transparent written by Jill Soloway, among many other items. This series is arranged alphabetically by author then alphabetically by title.
Series 7, SUBJECT FILES, 1988-2011, includes a small set of clippings, reports, notes, and other items collected by Bornstein on the following subjects: ACT Theatre Company, LGBT centers, sadomasochism, spirtuality/health, suicide, and transgenderism. This series is arranged alphabetically by subject.
Series 8, PRINT MATERIALS, 1980-2017, contains published books, calendars, catalogs, journals, magazine, reports, and a large collection of self-published zines by various artists and writers. Topics include comics, feminism, LGBTQ rights and religion, poetry, queer identity, queer critique of same sex marriage, sexuality, sex work, transgenderism, teens and teen girlhood, among many other topics. This subseries is arranged alphabetically by record type then title.
Series 9, EPHEMERA, 1991-2005, includes a small collection of items including buttons, drawings and illustrations, postcards, and stickers, many of which relate to lesbian, gay, bisexual, and transgender issues and activist causes. This series is arranged alphabetically by object type.
Series 10, PHOTOGRAPHS, 1910-2017, consists of one carton of black and white, color, and polaroid photographs documenting Albert and Kate Bornstein's family, relatives, friends, romantic partners, and events, dating from 1910-2017. Of particular interest are images of Albert Bornstein with mother, Mildred Vandam Bornstein, and brother, Alan Bornstein; Albert Bornstein and friends at Brown University; photographs from Albert Bornstein's weddings; photographs of Albert Bornstein with daughter, Jessica Leah Bornstein; photographs of Kate Bornstein shortly after gender reassignment surgery; and candid images of Kate alone and with friends and family. Series 10 is arranged alphabetically by subject.
Series 11, OVERSIZE MATERIALS, 1940-2006, includes posters documenting Bornstein's lectures and performances, get-well posters created for Bornstein while undergoing cancer treatment, an oversize book of photography by Jane Marcus, and fragile scrapbook pages containing Bornstein family photographs from 1940. Series 11 is arranged alphabetically by record type.
Series 12, ELECTRONIC RECORDS, 1977-2011, contains film, disks, cassettes, CDs, DVDs, and VHS tapes. Records include book and talk drafts, performances, photographs, and television appearances by Bornstein. Of particular interest are VHS tapes documenting Bornstein's early appearances on television shows such as 20/20 with Barbara Walters, the Joan Rivers Show, and the Phil Donahue Show where Bornstein discussed her experiences as a trans person. Bornstein's original carrier titles are written in quotations. The processor created all other folder titles. This series is arranged alphabetically by record type then by title on carrier.
Series 13, RESTRICTED, 1990-1995, contains a small set of files removed from throughout the collection, which are closed until January 1, 2039.
There are some restrictions on access, though most of the collection is open for research use. Series 13, Restricted, is closed until January 1, 2039 after which date the files will be open without restriction. The collection can only be seen by prior appointment because some materials may be stored off-site and cannot be produced on the same day on which they are requested.
This collection is arranged into 13 series.
Series 1, Biographical, 1910-2017 – arranged alphabetically by record type.
Series 2, Correspondence, 1977-2018 – arranged alphabetically by provenance.
Series 3, Diaries and notes, 1983-2015 – arranged alphabetically then chronologically.
Series 4, Conferences, 1991-2017– arranged chronologically.
Series 5, Writings by Kate, 1970-2013 – arranged alphabetically by title.
Series 6, Writings by other authors (unpublished), 1986-2014 – arranged alphabetically by author.
Series 7, Subject files, 1988-2011 – arranged alphabetically by topic.
Series 8, Print Materials, 1980-2017 – arranged alphabetically by record type then by title.
Series 9, Ephemera, 1991-2005 – arranged alphabetically by object type.
Series 10, Photographs, 1910-2017 – arranged alphabetically by subject.
Series 11, Oversize Materials, 1940-2006 – arranged alphabetically by record type.
Series 12, Electronic records, 1977-2011 – arranged alphabetically by record type.
Series 13, Restricted, 1990-1995 – arranged alphabetically by item.
Administrative information
Acquired from Kate Bornstein in 2018.
- Digital materials
  - novotesforbulliescontract.pages
    Original directory: Users/starbuck/Documents/Active/~Write Now/Date created: 2011-09-27 17:03:22 EDT-0400Date modified: 2011-09-27 17:03:22 EDT-0400MIME type: application/vnd.apple.pagesFile extension: pages
  - kb letter to the revolution for B.pages
  - Barbara Carrellas One Sheet Edit.pages
  - cheap sex with bc 2.pages
  - cheap sex with bc 3.pages
  - cheap sex with bc.pages
  - apology to neighbors.pages
  - Bornstein_letter_4_John_Emigh.pages
  - Justin V PS 122 Tribute.pages
  - KB_Endorses_Yetta_Kurland.pages
  - KB_Ltr_John_Emigh.pages
  - Not Guilty Plea—Bus Ticket.pages
  - Open Letter to Queer Youth Norway.pages
  - Rafe Posey Recc to Brown Grad School.pages
  - TORI LOR to JCHP.pages
  - Aiden Fyre LOR HRSA-NSP.pages
  - Aiden Fyre LOR NHSC.pages
  - Aiden Fyre LOR.pages
  - Crystal Letter page two.pages
  - Ltr Recc Crystal Yakacki OHSU.pages
  - KB recc for Laura.pages
  - KB_on_Hate_Crimes_Bill_4PHB.pages
  - Cast List Inherit the Earth.pages
  - Inherit the Earth notebook notes.pages
  - inherit the earth opening.pages
  - 1 KB Edit Chap 2.pages
  - 1 KB Edit TOC thru Chap 1.pages
  - 10 KB Edit Chap 10.pages
  - 11 KB Edit Gnite Gday and Acks.pages
  - 3 KB Edit Chap 3.pages
  - 5 KB Edit Chap 5.pages
  - 6 KB Edit Chap 6.pages
  - 7 KB Edit Chap 7.pages
  - 8 KB Edit Chap 8 copy.pages
  - 9 KB Edit Chap 9.pages
  - Author 1st proof AQs (Chap 3 to End).pages
  - Vested Interests Review.pages
  - Acceptance Speech KESHET 09.pages
  - Open Letter re Marriage Equality.pages
  - Intro All That Jazz.pages
  - Crossed Genres Interview.pages
  - Crossed Genres.pages
  - KateBornsteinRebelCupcake.pages
  - Performance Version Crossed Genres.pages
  - UCD_keynote_BC.pages
  - dvd case insert lana and kar.pages
  - dvd label 4 lana kar.pages
  - GOTNG Triangle Publishing Prize Acceptance Talk.pages
  - Kate Bornstein full clean edit.pages
  - Tku Lambda Lit Trans.pages
  - Dixie Belle June 2011.pages
  - Dixie Belle Reader 2011.pages
  - Sleeping Beauty.pages
  - B's pass_TOTWK_by_KB_for_OutMag.pages
  - TOTWK_by_KB_for_OutMag.pages
  - TOTWK_by_KB_OutMag.pages
  - Take Back the City Talk.pages
  - Gender Is A Wooly Worm 1st Draft 09.pages
  - 120502 Baldi GENDER OUTLAW China(2).pages
  - Gender Is A Caterpillar Introduction.pages
  - derby gender essay draft 5.pages
  - Gender Outlaw by Kate Bornstein and S. Bear Bergman.pages
  - gleanersGOTNG.pages
  - gotngdraft 3-Mar-2010.pages
  - gotngdraft 4-Feb-2010.pages
  - gotngdraft 4-Jan-2010.pages
  - Lucia Miel 1st draft KB notes.pages
  - Lucia Miel 1st draft.pages
  - LuMi_2.pages
  - On Men, Women and The Rest of Us AV.pages
  - Outlaws Last Gleaning.pages
  - Roz Second Poem.pages
  - Sassafrass Submission 1.pages
  - She-MaleRisingShawnaVirago.pages
  - HCW_Text_KBpass.pages
  - BalladOfLittleJo_by_Kate_B.pages
  - Beautiful Girls.pages
  - Brown Anthology Piece Text Bits.pages
  - Brown Piece.pages
  - Brown Reader Bornstein (edited2).pages
  - Brown Reader Bornstein (KBPass 1) clean.pages
  - Brown Reader Bornstein (KBPass 1).pages
  - Good Sportsmen.pages
  - GO TNG Blog.pages
  - what does mean mean.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 1.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 2.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 3.pages
  - Ltr to Design-Copyedit Team.pages
  - MNGW Please Read Me First.pages
  - Put with Pyramid.pages
  - Cautionary Interlude.pages
  - Limericks copy.pages
  - Limericks.pages
  - NWGW_Tweets from HG Pass.pages
  - TWEETS ETC.pages
  - TWEETS_only_kb_1st_sort.pages
  - Acknowledgments Plain.pages
  - Acknowledgements.pages
  - MNGW TOC and Intro.pages
  - 1 MNGW Chapter 1 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 1 Beta_EW.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 1 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 1.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 1_KBpass.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 1_sketch.pages
  - Start of the Journey.pages
  - exercise—coalition building.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 10 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 10 sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 10.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 9.pages
  - 2 MNGW Chapter 2 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 2 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 2 KB Pass.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 2 sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 2.pages
  - Treasure Map 1.pages
  - Kyriarchy Worksheer 2-up.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 3 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 3 KB Pass.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 3 Sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 3.pages
  - 4 MNGW Chapter 4 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 4 KB Pass.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 4 Sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 4.pages
  - 101 working table.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 5 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 5 KB pass.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 5 Sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 5.pages
  - 6 MNGW chapter 6 Gold sketch.pages
  - measuring sexuality by.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 6.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 6 Sketch.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 6_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 6_KB Pass.pages
  - MNGW chapter 7 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW chapter 7 sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 7.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 7_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 7_KB Pass.pages
  - 8 MNGW chapter 8 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW chapter 8 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW chapter 8 sketch.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 8_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 8_KB Pass copy.pages
  - MNGW chapter 9 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW chapter 9 sketch.pages
  - MNGW Old Chapter 8 Beta.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 9_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 9_KB Pass.pages
  - Old Exercises Where Gender Is.pages
  - BalladOfLittleJo_by_Kate_B.pages
  - best wishes for laura ingraham.pages
  - Tao of Mitzvah Sabbath Boddhisatva.pages
  - Transgender Day Remembrance 09.pages
  - william paterson piece.pages
  - betsey_girls_saved_my_life.pages
  - keynote notes beyond the binary.pages
  - GASP 1.pages
  - Cover Sketch 2 by KB .pages
  - cover sketch.pages
  - MNGW BW if it were KBs notebook.pages
  - MNGW BW w ruby slippers.pages
  - MNGW if it were KBs notebook.pages
  - MNGW rainbow anarchy trans line art ruby slippers KB note.pages
  - MNGW rainbow anarchy trans ruby slippers KB note.pages
  - MNGW rainbow anarchy trans ruby slippers.pages
  - MNGW Rainbow w Ruby Slippers.pages
  - MNGW Rainbow w Unicorn.pages
  - rainbow back cover beta 1.pages
  - Author 1st proof AQs (Prelims to Chap 2).pages
  - MNGW As to copy editor Qs January 3.pages
  - MNGW Qs to author December 7.pages
  - MNGW Uncle Stinky Where.pages
  - KB Edits Summary MNGW 2nd Proofs.pages
  - MNGW 1st Printing Errata.pages
  - 0 MNGW TOC & Intro.pages
  - 1 MNGW Chapter 1_KBpass.pages
  - 10 MNGW Chapter 10.pages
  - 2 MNGW Chapter 2 KB Pass (Kate Bornstein's conflicted copy 2012-10-21).pages
  - 2 MNGW Chapter 2 KB Pass.pages
  - 3 MNGW Chapter 3 KB Pass.pages
  - 4 MNGW Chapter 4 KB Pass.pages
  - 5 MNGW Chapter 5 KB pass.pages
  - 6 MNGW_chapter 6_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - 6 Sex Sex Sex Changes Accepted.pages
  - 7 MNGW_chapter 7_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - 8 MNGW_chapter 8_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - 9 MNGW_chapter 9_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - MNGW Website Marker Page.pages
  - My Old Gender Workbook MASTER.pages
  - My Old Gender Workbook Working Copy.pages
  - MyGenderWorkbook Update Thoughts.pages
  - raw thank you tweets.pages
  - 01 Welcome to Your Workbook.pages
  - 02 Solving the Gender Puzzle.pages
  - 03 Be All You Can Be, Fuck Your Gender, Love Sex Desire.pages
  - 04 Just Say No.pages
  - 05 Just Say Yes, Zen & Art of Gender Maintenance.pages
  - 06 The Playgrounds.pages
  - 07 Cautionary thru Revolutionary.pages
  - QueerAndPleasantProposal.pages
  - THE Acknowledgments.pages
  - FM-BornsteinED - with SL edits—KB Pass 2.pages
  - FM-BornsteinED - with SL edits—KB Pass.pages
  - MS-BornsteinED - with SL edits—KB Pass.pages
  - MS-BornsteinED - with SL edits—KB Pass2.pages
  - 1st QPD Press Release.pages
  - Blurb Letter Janet Reitman copy.pages
  - Blurb Letter Jeffrey Eugenides.pages
  - Blurb Letter Jenny Boylan.pages
  - Blurb Letter Patti Smith.pages
  - Blurb Letter Samuel Delany copy.pages
  - Letter to Librarian Galley Readers.pages
  - Letter to Media Galley Readers.pages
  - Kate proposal.pages
  - Bornstein Edit Salon 2-2.pages
  - kb contacts for tony o.pages
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger GOLD.pages
  - Dedication-Acknowledgments.pages
  - Book 2 Chap 4 Family Man.pages
  - Family Man copy.pages
  - Family Man.pages
  - text to grab 4 New York the First Time.pages
  - 0-Introduction.pages
  - 2-4.pages
  - 2-5.pages
  - 2-6.pages
  - 3-1 I Meet Daddy Man to Man.pages
  - 3-2 Borderline.pages
  - 3-3 Stages Of Life.pages
  - 3-4 OK This Is Where It Gets Complicated.pages
  - 3-5 Girl.pages
  - 3-2 after the big cut and paste.pages
  - 3-2 Borderline Old.pages